<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About me on Jan-Pieter D&#39;Anvers</title>
    <link>https://danversjp.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About me on Jan-Pieter D&#39;Anvers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://danversjp.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Other projects</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Engineering and science communications have always been passions of mine. However, I&amp;rsquo;m always looking forward to broaden my horizon with new and challenging projects. A non-exhaustive (and quite random) list of projects and experiences in which I took part can be found below.
  Exploitation of research: technology &amp;amp; knowledge transfer:
5 days training on research valorisation by KU Leuven Research &amp;amp; Development (LRD), including sessions on intellectual property law, industry collaboration and exploitation plans and with a hands-on project on validation of research results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Communication</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/sciencecommunication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/sciencecommunication/</guid>
      <description>Wetenschapsbattle / Battle of the Scientists:
Science communication challenge: present your research to children age 6-12. I was selected of one of the five finalists and presented my work to an audience of 3500 children. (in dutch) [link]
  Science figured out: How to keep a secret?:
3 minute video presentation on the need for post-quantum cryptography and side-channel attacks for a broad audience (in dutch) [link]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>A Side-Channel Resistant Implementation of SABER
with Michiel Van Beirendonck, Angshuman Karmakar, Josep Balasch, Ingrid Verbauwhede, ACM Journal on Emerging Technologies in Computing Systems 2020 [eprint]
  (One) Failure Is Not an Option: Bootstrapping the Search for Failures in Lattice-Based Encryption Schemes
with Mélissa Rossi and Fernando Virdia, Eurocrypt 2020 [eprint] [video]
  Exploiting Decryption Failures in Mersenne Number Cryptosystems
with Marcel Tiepelt, APKC 2020 [eprint]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in the COSIC research group at KU Leuven, Belgium under the supervision of Ingrid Verbauwhede and Frederik Vercauteren. I research the security and efficiency of post-quantum cryptography, with a focus on lattice-based cryptography. I&amp;rsquo;m involved in the development of the encryption algorithm Saber, which is one of the candidates for standardization in the NIST post-quantum standardization process.
 That was gobbledigook to me, now in human language?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>