<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About me on Jan-Pieter D&#39;Anvers</title>
    <link>https://danversjp.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About me on Jan-Pieter D&#39;Anvers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://danversjp.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD defence</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/phddefence2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/phddefence2/</guid>
      <description>My PhD defence will take place on May 28th, at 1pm. I will update this page with the link to follow my defence online once it is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD defence</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/phddefence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 16:48:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/phddefence/</guid>
      <description>I defended my PhD titled &amp;ldquo;Design and Security Analysis of Lattice-based Post-Quantum Encryption&amp;rdquo; on May 28th.
My PhD thesis can be found [here]. A recording of my defence can be found [here]. This presentation is aimed at a broad audience and should be followable without background knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other projects</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Engineering and science communications have always been passions of mine. However, I&amp;rsquo;m always looking forward to broaden my horizon with new and challenging projects. A non-exhaustive (and quite random) list of projects and experiences in which I took part can be found below.
  Exploitation of research: technology &amp;amp; knowledge transfer:
5 days training on research valorisation by KU Leuven Research &amp;amp; Development (LRD), including sessions on intellectual property law, industry collaboration and exploitation plans and with a hands-on project on validation of research results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Communication</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/sciencecommunication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/sciencecommunication/</guid>
      <description>Wetenschapsbattle / Battle of the Scientists:
Science communication challenge: present your research to children age 6-12. I was selected of one of the five finalists and presented my work to an audience of 3500 children. (in dutch) [link]
  Science figured out: How to keep a secret?:
3 minute video presentation on the need for post-quantum cryptography and side-channel attacks for a broad audience (in dutch) [link]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Multitarget decryption failure attacks and their application to Saber and Kyber
with Senne Batsleer, Cryptology ePrint Archive, Report 2021/193 [eprint]
  Attacking and Defending Masked Polynomial Comparison for Lattice-Based Cryptography
with Shivam Bhasin, Daniel Heinz, Thomas Pöppelmann and Michiel Van Beirendonck, IACR Transactions on Cryptographic Hardware and Embedded Systems (TCHES) 2021 [eprint] [video]
  Error Term Checking: Towards Chosen Ciphertext Security without Re-encryption
with Emmanuela Orsini and Frederik Vercauteren, ACM ASIA Public-Key Cryptography Workshop 2021 (Best paper award) [eprint]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://danversjp.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danversjp.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>I’m a post-doctoral researcher in the COSIC research group at KU Leuven, Belgium.
My research interests include development, security and side-channel secure implementation of post-quantum encryption. I’m involved in the development of the encryption algorithm Saber, which is one of the candidates for standardization in the NIST post-quantum standardization process.
 That was gobbledigook to me, now in human language?  Cryptography is the study of secure communication, for example encrypting messages into a secret code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>